CRISTOPER CASTRO

WEB DEVELOPER











PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with a year of experience in website design and application. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail. With my versatile skill set, efficiency, and commitment to delivering exceptional service make me the best fit for the role of Web Developer.

SKILLS

- WordPress | Shopify | Squarespace |
- Webflow
- HTML | CSS | JavaScript
- Graphic Design
- Problem-Solving
- Video Editing
- SEO
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

SHOPIFY STORE WEB DEVELOPER

U PICK A PALLET LLC

December 2022 - March 2023

- Create and Design for the client's website
- Add Store Products, Chat Bot, and Membership
- Evaluate website layout, SEO, and functionality

SHOPIFY WEB DEVELOPER

Love and Lashes UK

April 2023 - July 2023

- Create and Design for the client's website
- Create and Add product design
- Evaluate website layout, SEO, and functionality

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

STI Senior High School

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

STI College

2015 - 2017

2018 - 2022

SHOPIFY STORE WEB DEVELOPER

Hurstville Aquarium

August 2023 - October 2023

- Create and Design for the client's website
- Create and Add product design
- Evaluate website layout, SEO, and functionality